你们看  丑裸男在收拾东西
Oh hey, you guys, look! Ugly Naked Guy is putting stuff in boxes!
看样子我们的裸友要搬家了
I'd say from the looks of it; our naked buddy is moving.
讽刺的是
Ironically,
大部分的箱子都标示着"衣服"
most of the boxes seem to be labeled clothes.
我会怀念那个软软的大屁股的
Ohh, I'm gonna miss that big old squishy butt.
鸡肉炒饭吃不下去了
And we're done with the chicken fried rice.
如果他要搬走  我可以去把那里租下来
Hey! Hey! If he's moving, maybe I should try to get his place!
好主意
Good idea!
跟你们遥遥相对多好玩啊
It would be so cool to live across from you guys!
那我们就可以玩电话游戏
Hey, yeah! Then we could do that telephone thing!
你一个罐子
Y'know, you have a can,
我们一个罐子  中间有一条线
we have a can and it's connected by a string!
或者我们也可以打真的电话
Or we can do the actual telephone thing.
天哪  我爱死这间公寓了  很完美吧
Oh my God! I love this apartment! Isn't it perfect?!
我居然没发现这里有这么棒
I can't believe I never realized how great it is!
因为你的目光会马上移到大块头裸男身上
Well that is because your eye immediately goes to the big naked man.
太棒了  你最好赶快
It's amazing! You better hurry up
去申请  否则我会抢先
and fill out an application or I'm gonna beat you to it.
没想到会有这一天
Well, I never thought I'd say this,
我要去用丑裸男的厕所了
but I'm gonna go use Ugly Naked Guy's bathroom.
你看  是莫妮卡和钱德勒
Oh, look! There's Monica and Chandler!
喂  你们好  喂
Hey! Hey, you guys! Hey!
钱德勒和莫妮卡  钱德勒和莫妮卡
Ahhh!! Chandler and Monica!! Chandler and Monica!!
天哪
Oh my God!
钱德勒和莫妮卡
Chandler and Monica!!!!
天哪
Oh my God!!!
我要瞎了  我要瞎了
Oh!! My eyes!!! My eyes!!!!
菲比  菲比  没事的
Phoebe!! Phoebe!! It's okay!! It's okay!!
不  他们搞在一起
No! They're doing it!!!
我知道  我知道
I Know!! I know!! I know!
你知道
You know?!!!
对  我知道  乔伊也知道
Yes, I know! And Joey knows!
但罗斯不知道  所以你别再叫了
But Ross doesn't know so you have to stop screaming!!
怎么了
What's going on?
What?! What?!
没事  我们只是好兴奋
Nothing! Oh God, we're just so excited
你要搬来这里
that you want to get this apartment!
这里的确很棒
Actually, it looks really good.
快过来啊
Get in here!!!
你是说每次莫妮卡和钱德勒
You mean whenever Monica and Chandler where like
去洗衣服或买东西或...
y'know doing laundry or going grocery shopping or-Oh!
她每次跟露营认识的伤心琳达讲电话
All that time Monica spent on the phone with sad Linda from camp!
嘿咻  嘿咻  色情电话
Uh-huh, doing it. Doing it. Phone doing it.
真不敢相信
Oh, I can't believe it!
真是太好了  对男方来说
I mean I think it's great! For him.
女方可以找个更好的
She might be able to do better.
你们好
Hey guys!
-乔伊  快过来  -怎么啦
- Joey! Come here! Come here! - What? What?
菲比发现了莫妮卡和钱德勒的事
Phoebe just found out about Monica and Chandler.
就是他们是朋友  如此而已吗
You mean how they're friends and nothing more?
不  乔伊  她知道了
No. Joey, she knows!
我们刚才在丑裸男的公寓
We were at Ugly Naked Guy's apartment
看到他们隔着窗户在做
and we saw them doing it through the window.
应该说是靠着窗户在做
Actually, we saw them doing it up against the window.
所以说  他们知道你知道
Okay, so now they know that you know
但是不知道瑞秋知道吗
and they don't know that Rachel knows?
对  知道吗
Yes, but y'know what?
谁知道什么都不重要了
It doesn't matter who knows what.
我们三个人都知道了  就可以告诉他们了
Now, enough of us know that we can just tell them that we know!
我再也不必说谎保密了
Then all the lying and the secrets would finally be over!
或者也可以不告诉他们  咱们来找点乐子
Or, we could not tell them we know and have a little fun of our own.
什么意思
Wh-what do you mean?
譬如每次他们说要洗衣服
Well y'know every time that they say that like they're doing laundry
我们就给他们一堆衣服洗
we'll just give them a bunch of laundry to do.
我喜欢
Ohhh, I-I would enjoy that!
不不不  瑞秋
No-no-no! No-no wait Rach,
你知道怎样更好玩吗  告诉他们
you know what would even be more fun? Telling them.
不  我想照菲比说的做
Ehhh, no, I wanna do Phoebe's thing.
我没办法再...
I can't take any...
不用你做什么  你只要别说我们知道就行了
No! You don't have to do anything! Just don't tell them that we know!
不要  我没办法再保密了
Noo! I can't take any more secrets!
我有你们的秘密  他们的秘密
I've got your secrets. I've got their secrets.
还有我自己的秘密
I got secrets of my own y'know!
你才没有秘密
You don't have any secrets!
是吗  你就不知道我睡觉时要抱着
Oh yeah? Well, you don't know about Hugsy,
企鹅"抱宝"
my bedtime penguin pal.
所以  我们要怎么耍他们
So umm, how-how are we gonna mess with them?
你可以利用室友的身份
Well, you could use your position y'know as the roommate.
我就运用我最大的本钱
And then. I would use y'know the strongest tool at my disposal.
我的性感
My sexuality.
孩子们
Hello children!
看仔细了  学着点  别吃我的饼干
Okay, watch, learn, and don't eat my cookie.
你穿这件外套真好看
Ooh, wow that jacket looks great on you!
是吗
Really?
对  这个料子摸起来好软
Yeah the material feels so soft-
你好  二头肌先生
hello Mr. Bicep!
你有在健身吗
Have you been working out?
我有在挤牙膏
Well, I try to y'know, squeeze things.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
如果你真的想知道  我不能告诉你
Well, if you really wanna know, I'm-Oh! I can't tell you this.
菲比  你什么都可以告诉我
Phoebe, it's me. You can tell me anything.
事实上我就是不能告诉你
Well actually you're the one person I can't tell this too.
但我又最想告诉你
And the one person I want to the most.
怎么了
What's going on?
因为我很久没有谈恋爱了
I think it's just y'know that I haven't been with a guy in so long
有时你一直寻寻觅觅
and how sometimes you're looking for something
却没发现
and you just don't even see that
他就在你眼前喝咖啡
it's right there in front of you sipping coffee-
我说太多了吗
Oh no, have I said to much?
总之值得考虑一下  我就会考虑
Well it's just something to think about. I know I will.
你好可爱
You are so cute!
你怎么会这么可爱
How did you get to be so cute?
我爷爷是瑞典人
Well, my Grandfather was Swedish
我奶奶其实是只拇指兔
and my Grandmother was actually a tiny little bunny.
你变得更可爱了
Okay, now you're even cuter!!
-这简直是今天的民意  -什么
- Y'know that is a popular opinion today I must say. - What?
今天在咖啡馆有一件怪事
The weirdest thing happened at the coffee house, I think,
我觉得菲比在钓我
I think Phoebe was hitting on me.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
是真的  菲比觉得我很有魅力
I'm telling you I think Phoebe thinks I'm foxy.
不可能
That's not possible!
抱歉  只是在菲比眼中
I'm sorry it's just, Phoebe just always thought you were,
你的魅力是没有男性吸引力的
you were charming in a, in a sexless kind of way.
这种话真是百听不厌
Oh, y'know I-I can't hear that enough.
抱歉  你应该误解她的意思了
I'm sorry, I think that you just misunderstood her.
我没有误解  好吗
No, I didn't misunderstand, okay?
她对我上下其手  她还摸我的二头肌呢
She was all over me! She touched my bicep for crying out loud!
这个二头肌
This bicep?
我现在没挤它好吧
Well it's not flexed right now!
莫妮卡  你现在有事吗
Hey Mon, what are you doing now?
要不要一起去看电影
Wanna come see a movie with us?
事实上  我正要去洗衣服
Uhh, y'know actually I was gonna do some laundry.
钱德勒  要不要一起去
Hey Chandler, wanna do it with me?
-好啊  我跟你一起去  -好的
- Sure, I'll do it with ya. - Okay.
太好了  等一下
Okay great, hold on a sec!
拿去
Oh, here you go!
不介意吧  帮了我的大忙了  多谢
You don't mind do ya? That would really help me out a lot! Thanks!
我的硬币应该不够
I mean I-I don't I think I have enough quarters.
我这里有
I have quarters!
罗斯  公寓申请得怎样
Hey Ross! Any word on the apartment yet?
我打过去问  原来
Well, I called over there and it turns out
丑裸男要自己转租
Ugly Naked Guy is subletting it himself
而且已经有一大堆申请者了
and he's already had like a hundred applicants.
我占了优势
I've got the edge.
我知道这样有点奸诈  但我送了点东西
I know it's not exactly ethical but I sent him a little bribe to
去贿赂他
tip the scales in my direction.
来吧  从窗户说不定能看到
Check it out, you can probably see it from the window.
是那个打了蝴蝶结的弹球机吗
Oh, is it that pinball machine with the big bow on it?
不是
No.
那辆新的山地车
That new mountain bike?
不是
No.
那你送的是什么
Well what did you send?
一篮小松饼
A basket of mini-muffins.
但桌上全都是小松饼篮
But there's a whole table of mini-muffin baskets.
哪一篮是你送的
Which one did you send?
小的那一篮
The small one.
你真以为那篮松饼
What?! You-you actually thought
能帮你争取到公寓吗
that basket was gonna get you the apartment?
对啊  我们办公室曾经收到一篮
Well yeah! Someone sent us a basket at work once
大家都爱得不得了
and people went crazy over those little muffins.
那天真的好开心
It was the best day.
你的工作让我觉得好伤心
Your work makes me sad.
真是的  我好想要那间公寓
Oh man! I want that place so much!!
我还以为一定会成功的
I was so sure that was gonna work!
那十二块算是扔到水里了
There's twelve bucks I'll never see again!
亲爱的  想看电影就得快了
All right honey, we'd better go if we wanna catch that movie.
再见
Bye!
钱德勒再见  我已经开始想你了
Bye Chandler! I miss you already.
看到了吗  她嗲声嗲气还捏我
Okay, did you see that?! With the inappropriate and the pinching!!
我看到了
Actually, I did!
你现在相信她对我有意思了吧
Okay, so now do you believe that she's attracted to me?
天哪  她知道我们的事了
Ohhh, oh my God! Oh my God! She knows about us!
真的吗
Are you serious?
菲比知道了  她想吓我们
Phoebe knows and she's just trying to freak us out!
这是唯一的解释
That's the only explanation for it!
那我好捏的屁股
Okay but what about y'know my pinchable butt
和激凸的二头肌呢
and my bulging biceps-
她知道了
She knows!
-乔伊  -什么事
- Joey. - Yeah?
菲比知道我们的事了
Phoebe knows about us!
我没告诉她们
Well I didn't tell them!
她们  她们是谁
Them?! Who's them?
菲比和乔伊
Uhhh, Phoebe and Joey.
乔伊
Joey.
和瑞秋
And Rachel.
我想告诉你们的  但她们让我保证不说
I would've told you but they made me promise not to tell!
-老天  -对不起  那现在没事了吧
- Oh man! - I'm sorry! But hey, it's over now, right?
你们可以告诉她们  你们知道她们知道了
Because you can tell them that you know they know
我就可以恢复一无所知了
and I can go back to knowing absolutely nothing!
除非
Unless...
没有除非  现在就要了结
No! Not unless! Look this must end now!
她们还自以为高明想耍我们
Oh man, they think they are so slick messing with us!
她们不知道  我们知道她们知道了
But see they don't know that we know that they know!
所以
So...
没错  耍人的变成了被耍的
Ahh yes, the messers become the messies!
惨了
Noooo.
罗斯  别再折磨自己了
Oh Ross, honey you gotta stop torturing yourself!
你去找别的房子嘛
Yeah, why don't you just find another apartment?
我这个月已经看了上千套公寓了
Look I've already looked at like a thousand apartments this month
没一间能比得上那一间
and none of them even compares to that one!
你知道你应该怎么做吗
Y'know what you should do?
你应该找出他的嗜好
You should find out what his hobbies are
拿来跟他套交情
and then use that to bond with him.
例如  如果我对乔伊有所求
Yeah! Like if I would want something from Joey,
我就会聊  三明治
I would strike up a conversation about say umm, sandwiches.
或是我的内衣
Or uh, or my underwear.
我在听
I'm listening.
-看到没  -好棒的主意
- See? - That is a great idea!
而且我了解丑裸男
And! I know Ugly Naked Guy
因为我们偷窥他五年了
because we've been watching him for like five years
所以我又重新占了上风
so that gives me back my edge!
想想看  他有一张蹦床
Oh, let's see now he had the trampoline.
被他跳坏了
He broke that.
他有一双重力靴
Well, he had gravity boots.
也被他穿坏了
Yeah, he broke those too.
所以他喜欢破坏东西
So he likes to break stuff.
我得去接本
Okay, I've got to go pick up Ben
不过我会想出来的
but I-I will figure something out.
他之前是不是有一只猫
Hey, didn't he used to have a cat?
别提那个  会害他心情不好
I wouldn't bring that up, it would probably just bum him out.
可怜的猫咪  没看到大屁股压下来
Yeah, poor cat, never saw that big butt coming.
喂
Hello.
在  等一下  她就在旁边
Oh yeah! Hey! Hold on a second she's right here!
钱德勒找你
It's Chandler.
你好啊
Hello you.
你好  菲比  我一整天都在想你
Hello Phoebe, I've been thinking about you all day.
你之前的提议
Well you know that thing you said before,
我不心动是骗人的
I'd be lying if I said I wasn't intrigued.
是吗
Really?
对  乔伊晚上不在
Yeah, listen, Joey isn't gonna be here tonight
不如你过来  我让你
so why don't you come over and I'll let you uh,
摸我的二头肌  甚至是别的地方
feel my bicep. Or maybe more.
我待会再给你答复  再见
I'll have to get back to you on that. Okay, bye!
天哪  他让我去摸他的二头肌和别的地方
Oh my God! He wants me to come over and feel his bicep and more!
-开玩笑吗  -真的
- Are you kidding?! - No!
他居然背着莫妮卡...
I can not believe he would do that to Mon-
-乔伊  他们知道我们知道了吗  -不知道
- Joey, do they know that we know? - No.
乔伊
Joey.
他们知道你们知道了
They know you know.
我就知道
Ugh, I knew it!
那两个人真不像话
Oh I cannot believe those two!
他们以为他们可以耍我们
God, they thought they can mess with us!
想耍我们耶
They're trying to mess with us?!
他们不知道  我们知道他们知道我们知道了
They don't know that we know they know we know!
乔伊  你不能说
Joey, you can't say anything!
我想说也说不清
I couldn't even if I wanted too.
晚上好  先生  我是罗斯·盖勒
Good evening, sir. My name is Ross Geller.
我申请了要租你的房子
I'm one of the people who applied for the apartment.
我知道竞争很激烈  但是
And I-I realize that the competition is fierce but-
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我注意到你光着身体
I, I can't help but notice you're naked and
我为你鼓掌  我也好想光着
I applaud you. Man, I wish I was naked.
看起来太棒了
I mean, this-this looks so great.
这正是上帝造人的本意
That is how God intended it.
你看她们多慌
Look at them, they're-they're panicked!
-她们绝对会退缩  -没错
- Oh yeah, they're totally gonna back down! - Oh yeah!
好吧  他敢约我就敢去
All right. All right! If he wants a date? He's gonna get a date.
我要过去了
All right, I'm gonna go in.
性感一点
All right. Be sexy.
拜托
Please.
钱德勒  我晚上可以过去
So Chandler, I-I'd love to come by tonight.
是嘛
Really?
-当然  就七点吧  -好的
- Oh absolutely. Shall we say, around seven? - Yes.
好的  我很期待跟你
Good. I'm really looking forward to you
发生性关系
and me having sexual intercourse.
快来看  快来看
Hey-hey, check it out! Check it out!
丑裸男有裸友来访
Ugly Naked Guy has a naked friend!
是啊
Oh yeah!
天哪  那是我们的朋友
Oh my God! That is our friend!
是裸罗斯
It's Naked Ross!
好戏开场
Show time!
-瑞秋  拿香水来  -好的
- Okay, Rachel, get me perfume! - Okay!
乔伊  帮我拿瓶酒和杯子
And Joey, get me a bottle of wine and glasses?
放心好了
All right, it'll be great!
只要让她以为  你想跟她上床
You just make her think you wanna have sex with her!
她绝对会吓到
It'll totally freak her out!
我到底得撑到什么程度
Okay, listen, how far am I gonna have to go with her?
别紧张  她会比你先投降
Relax, she-she's gonna give in way before you do!
你怎么知道
How do you know?!
因为你跟我是一队的  我这一队总是赢
Because you're on my team! And my team always wins!
赢这种事
At this?!
总之去吓她  快去
Just go get some!  Go!
亲爱的  我会站在门外听
Okay honey, now I'm gonna try to listen from right here! Okay.
等一下
Okay? Whoa, wait!
-好主意  -等等
- Good idea! - Yeah, oh wait!
别把料都爆光了
Oh now, don't give away the farm!
菲比
Phoebe.
钱德勒
Chandler.
进来吧
Come on in.
我正要进去
I was going too.
我带了酒来  你要吗
Umm, I brought some wine. Would you like some?
好啊
Sure.
要开始了  紧张吗
So, here we are. Nervous?
我  不会  你呢
Me? No. You?
不会  这样正合我意
No, I want this to happen.
我也是
So do I.
我去放点音乐
I'm gonna put on some music.
我跳舞给你看好了
Maybe, maybe I'll dance for you.
你真美
You look good.
谢谢
Thanks!
你说这种话
Y'know, that when you say things like that
让我好想扯掉你的毛衣背心
it makes me wanna rip that sweater vest right off!
不如进房里再说吧
Well, why don't we move this into the bedroom?
真的吗
Really?
你不想吗
Oh, do you not want to?
不是
No. No!
只是我想先脱掉衣服
It's just y'know first, I wanna take off all my clothes
让你替我擦乳液
and have you rub lotion on me.
听起来不错
Well that would be nice.
我去拿乳液
I'll go get the lotion.
情况完全失控了
Listen, this is totally getting out of hand! Okay?
她要我帮她擦乳液
She wants me to put lotion on her!
她在唬你
She's bluffing!
她没打算放弃  她还这样
Look, she's not backing down! She went like this!
他没打算放弃  他去拿乳液了
He's not backing down. He went to get lotion.
真是的  你们还没好吗
Oh man! Aren't you guys done yet?!
我想坐我的椅子
I wanna sit in my chair!
乔伊  这样想
Joey look, just look at it this way,
菲比一突破钱德勒的防线
the sooner Phoebe breaks Chandler
这一切就结束公开了
the sooner this is all over and out in the open.
我喜欢
I like that!
让他看你的胸罩  他怕胸罩
Oh, okay! Show him your bra! He's afraid of bras!
他解不开
Can't work 'em!
乔伊
Joey!
你没有扯掉扣子
Wow, you didn't rip off any buttons.
老经验了
It's not my first time.
你给我回去  色诱到她屈服为止
You go back out there and you seduce her till she cracks!
等一下  你打扫过了吗
Okay, give me a second! Did you clean up in here?
当然
Of course.
你要走了吗
Oh, you're-you're going?
除非你跟我走  爱人
Umm, not without you, lover.
这是我的胸罩
So, this is my bra.
很好看
It's very, very nice.
过来  我很高兴我们要做爱了
Well, come here. I'm very happy we were gonna be having all the sex.
你是该高兴  我的身体很柔软
You should be. I'm very bendy.
我要吻你了
I'm gonna kiss you now.
除非我先吻你
Not if I kiss you first.
看来接下来就只能接吻了
Well, I guess there's nothing left for us to do but-but kiss.
终于来了  我们的初吻
Here it comes. Our first kiss.
好啦  你赢了  我不能跟你上床
Okay! Okay! Okay! You win! You win!! I can't have sex with ya!
为什么
And why not?!
因为我爱莫妮卡
Because I'm in love with Monica!!
你什么
You're-you're what?!
我爱她  没错  我爱她  我爱她
Love her! That's right, I...love...her!!! I love her!!
我爱你  莫妮卡
I love you, Monica.
我也爱你  钱德勒
I love you too Chandler.
我以为你们只是搞在一起
I just-I thought you guys were doing it,
我不知道你们相爱了
I didn't know you were in love!
兄弟
Dude!
向菲比致敬  强劲的对手
And hats off to Phoebe. Quite a competitor.
此外你的胸部还晾在外面
And might I say your breasts are still showing.
天哪
God!
太好了  结束了  大家都知道了
All right! So that's it! It's over! Everybody knows!
罗斯还不知道
Well actually, Ross doesn't.
对  请你们先别告诉他
Yes, and we'd appreciate it if no one told him yet.
新罗斯的新家
A new place for a new Ross.
我一布置好就请你
I'm gonna have you and all the guys from work over
和同事来坐
once it's y'know, furnished.
很高兴看到你重新振作
I must say it's nice to see you back on your feet.
我是振作了  脾气暴躁的事都过去了
Well I am that. And that whole rage thing is definitely behind me.
你是不是该回馆里上班了
I wonder if its time for you to rejoin our team at the museum?
那就太好了  唐纳德
Oh Donald that-that would be great.
我已经准备好重回岗位
I am totally ready to come back to work.
我...  什么  不
I-What? No!
你在干什么
Wh... What are you doing?!!
放开我妹妹
Get off my sister!